bigwinds.com 2015-07-23

# Our Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy 

Big Winds respects your privacy. We will never rent or sell your personal information or willingly share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties. Big Winds is committed to privacy and security for all of our customers. We have developed the following Privacy Statement: 

### Personal Information

Under no circumstances do we transfer your email address to any other company, nor do we collect any personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs. 

There are two ways you can provide us with, and consent to our collection of certain personal information: 

**E-mail Request** \- Links throughout our site provide you with the opportunity to contact us via e-mail to ask questions, request information or provide comments and suggestions. You may also be offered the opportunity to have one of our sales staff contact you to provide additional information about our products or services. To do so, we may request additional personal information from you, such as your name and telephone number, to help us satisfy your request. 

**Enrollment** \- You may choose to enroll for one of our products or services where we will request certain information from you. Depending on the type of product or service that you request, you may be asked to provide personal information. For certain products and services, we may require your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and credit card number. Other products and services may require different or supplemental information from you in order to apply. 

### Our Website Analytics

Information obtained while visiting our site does not identify you personally, but rather records information about a visit to our site. We may monitor statistics such as number of visits, popular pages and browser use. We use statistics about your visit to help us improve website performance and its user experience. 

### Opt-Out of Notifications

Periodically, we notify our customers of new products, sales and upcoming events. If you would like to opt-out of our notifications, please contact us at bigwinds@bigwinds.com.
